Over the Pacific Ocean moving towards Baja California
Over Baja California looking north towards the United States
Over Mexico heading towards the south-west United States
Over the south-west United States
Over the Rocky Mountains approaching Denver
Travelling over the Great Plains of the United States
Approaching the Great Lakes with Ontario, Canada beyond
Over the Great Lakes approaching Ontario, Canada
The Aurora Borealis over western Ontario, Canada
The Aurora Borealis over northern Ontario, Canada
The Aurora Borealis over northern Quebec, Canada
Heading towards the North Atlantic with the Aurora Borealis over Labrador, Canada